musafir.com 2013-05-02

# Privacy policy

We understand that making purchases online involves a great deal of trust on your part. We take this trust very seriously, and make it our highest priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us. Please read the following policy to learn about our privacy practices.

The terms "we", "us", "our" and "Musafir" refer to Universal Travels & Tourism LLC, a limited liability company incorporated in Sharjah, United Arab Emirates. The term "you" refers to the customer visiting the Website and/or booking a reservation through us on this Website, or through our customer service agents. By visiting the Musafir.com website (the "Website"), you are accepting the practices described herein.

### What information we collect from you

  * In General. We receive and store any information you enter on our Website or give us in any other way. This includes information that can identify you ("personal information"), including your first and last name, telephone number, postal and e-mail addresses. We also may request information about your traveler preferences, including meal requests, seat selection, frequent flyer/hotel/car rental program information, and ticketing options. You can choose not to provide information to us, but in general some information about you is required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; complete a traveler profile; participate in a survey, contest, or sweepstakes; ask us a question; or initiate other transactions on our site.
  * Passenger Information. When you make travel or other arrangements for someone else through Musafir.com, we will request personal information and travel preferences about that individual. You should obtain the consent of other individuals prior to providing Musafir.com with their personal information and travel preferences, as any access to view or change their information will be available only through your account.
  * Information from Other Sources. We also may periodically obtain information about you from our business partners and other independent third-party sources and add it to our account information. Examples of information we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, which we use to correct our records and to facilitate proper delivery of travel information; and demographic information, which we use to better understand your potential purchasing preferences.
  * Automatic Information. We automatically collect some information about your computer when you visit Musafir.com. For example, we will collect your IP address, Web browser software (such as Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer), and referring Website. We also may collect information about your online activity, such as trips viewed and purchases made. One of our goals in collecting this automatic information is to help customize your user experience.
  * Cookies and Other Web Technologies. When you visit Musafir.com, we may assign your computer a "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file). You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies from Musafir.com, you may not be able to access many of the travel tools offered by Musafir.com.
  * Information Collected by Third-Party Advertising Companies. Third-party advertisers, such as those we use to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet, may use cookies and other technologies (such as Web beacons or single-pixel GIFS) for several purposes, including: to measure the effectiveness of their ads; to analyze, modify, and personalize advertising content on Musafir.com and other sites; and to provide ads about goods and services we hope will be of interest to you. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers are not covered by this Privacy Policy. You can find out more about third-party advertisers and explore the option of not having this information collected by clicking here.

### How we protect your information

We want you to feel confident about using Musafir.com to plan and purchase your travel, so we are committed to protecting the information we collect. We have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they only may do so for permitted business functions.

In addition, we use 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption when transmitting your sensitive personal information between your system and our Website, and we employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your information.

All credit card transactions on Musafir.com are processed through a service provided by MashreqBank PSC on behalf of MasterCard International, which uses 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption when transmitting your payment card details. We and Mashreqbank PSC do not receive and do not store sensitive billing information such as your credit card number, cardholder name, and expiration date.

Despite these measures, we do not warrant that unauthorized access to your information can never happen and will not be liable for any such unauthorized access unless caused solely by our gross negligence, in which event you will be entitled to compensation up to a maximum of the value of the services purchased by you.

### How we use your information

We use information about you for the following general purposes: to provide you with the products and services you request; to provide you with travel confirmation and updates; to manage your account, including processing bills and providing travel notifications; to communicate with you in general; to respond to your questions and comments; to measure interest in and improve our products, services, and Website; to notify you about special offers and products or services that may be of interest to you; to otherwise customize your experience with Musafir.com; to reward you as part of any reward and recognition program you choose to join; to solicit information from you, including through surveys; to resolve disputes, collect fees, or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

### With whom we share your information

Musafir.com may share your information with the following entities:

  * Suppliers, such as hotel, airline, cruise, or car rental companies, or activity providers, who fulfill your travel reservations. Throughout Musafir.com, all services provided by a third-party supplier are described as such. We do not share your email address with these suppliers unless they need it to fulfill the travel reservation you have made on Musafir.com, and we restrict their use of this information to that purpose. We do not place limitations on our suppliers' use or disclosure of your other personal information. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any travel supplier whose products you purchase through Musafir.com. Please note that these suppliers also may contact you as necessary to obtain additional information about you or to facilitate your travel reservation.
  * Third-party vendors who provide services or functions on our behalf, including credit card processing, business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution of surveys or sweepstakes programs, and fraud prevention. These companies have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use the information for any other purpose.
  * Business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service you have requested because their name will appear with ours. If you choose to access these optional services, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those partners. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners and recommend you evaluate their practices before deciding to provide your personal information.

### We also may share your information:

  * In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
  * When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of Musafir.com, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Service and other agreements.
  * In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.

We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors a Website receives or what are the most popular vacation destinations. This information does not contain any personal information and is used to develop content and services we hope you will find of interest.

### How you can access your information

You have the right to see personal information we keep about you upon payment of a fee. If you are concerned that any of the information we hold on you is incorrect please contact us.

### Your choices with respect to collection and use of your information

  * As discussed above, you can choose not to provide us with any information, although it may be needed to make travel purchases or to take advantage of certain features offered on Musafir.com.
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies from Musafir.com, you will not be able to access portions of our site.

### Children's privacy

Musafir.com does not sell travel or other services for purchase by children. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information.

### External Links

If any part of the Musafir.com Website links you to other websites, those websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Musafir.com may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

### How you can contact us

If you have questions about either this Privacy Policy (or your travel planning or purchases), please contact us at the following address:

Universal Travels & Tourism LLC  
Ibn Zaydoon Street  
Umm Al Tarafa, Rolla  
Post box 62425  
Sharjah, United Arab Emirates  
Phone: +971 6 516 6666  
Fax: +971 6 534 3338

Revised May 22, 2011.
